<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smarter Worlds</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Smarter Worlds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaming progress and procrastination</title>
      <link>/post/2018-11-04-gaming-progress-procrastination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-11-04-gaming-progress-procrastination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many games have achievement trackers that allow the player to aim for an arbitrary objective. The most sophisticated versions bundle objectives into groups that give a sense of a clear progression that hides the tedious steps required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;World of Warcraft is such and I&amp;rsquo;ve generally looked over these artificial achievements focusing instead of the more obvious level increase and zone discovery. Recently however things have changed and I&amp;rsquo;ve manage to go through several layers of repetitive game play with only the achievement system as a guide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why so many coins ?</title>
      <link>/post/2017-08-14-why-so-many-coins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-08-14-why-so-many-coins/</guid>
      <description>At the time of writing, there are 1059 cryptocurrencies listed of the coinmarketcap.com, ( the go-to website for price, market information ). The list starts with Bitcoin, Ethereum and Ripple at the top and ends with ELcoin, microCoin and Turbocoin.
The question : why do many coins ? Do we really need so many different digital currencies ? Is it even conceivable that even 50 of them have a stable long term future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized currency for the decentralized individual</title>
      <link>/post/2017-06-17-decentralized-currency-individual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 18:02:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-06-17-decentralized-currency-individual/</guid>
      <description>Crypto-currencies led by Bitcoin are surging. Adoption is growing and we are at a stage where innovation abounds.
Still today most people have even heard of Bitcoin or Ethereum or Litecoin. And there’s a need to comprehend what cryto-currencies mean in the larger context of human evolution.
A crypto-currency is first and foremost a decentralized means of exchange, store of value and more generally information propagation. Decentralized is the key term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As long as your brain is in motion</title>
      <link>/post/2017-06-16-only-brain-in-motion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 17:49:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-06-16-only-brain-in-motion/</guid>
      <description>So long as your brain is active, thinking and growing then you are.
Rigidity and decay that with how with think the evolving world around us. A constantly moving brain allows to use as many filters as need to engage with our universe.
The most important activity for brain growth and health is learning. Constant and varied learning.
From human languages to new workout, from new professional skills to new social behaviors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only a wish?</title>
      <link>/post/2017-06-15-only-a-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 17:47:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-06-15-only-a-wish/</guid>
      <description>How realistic can one be when longing for a smarter world to live in, for brighter minds to connect with ?
This world can be much smarter that it is today at the individual and collective levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m a progressive because</title>
      <link>/post/2017-06-18-progressive-because/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-06-18-progressive-because/</guid>
      <description>I believe that left to their our devices humans could veer towards inhumanity by unleashing their inner demons. History has taught us than humans can unleash horror.
The nazis weren&amp;rsquo;t aliens from another planet. They were human. And these humans devised and carried out a massive plan of torture and extermination.
This historic incident repeated itself in various forms and different levels of intensity with the Stalin purges, Pol Pot in Cambodia or even in Rwanda.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>